<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Doctor Profile

              Go to our Website: https://www.2ndro.com/

              Then go to Patient Registration Page

              Click on Admin / Doctor Login

              You will see this window

















































              Login

              In order to log in to the TeleHealth, a user needs to enter the following information in the Login
              Box.


                 User ID: This is the ID provided to a user by the application administrator.
                 Password: This is the password set by the user.


              Click on the Submit button to gain access.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[Forgot Password


              A user can click on the Forgot Password link to reset a forgotten password. The user is then
              prompted to enter his/her User ID and the registered Email Address Upon verification of the
              same, the user will receive an email with a new password which can  be changed after signing
              in.


              Doctor Profile has 2 tabs:
                 1.  Patient Worklist
                 2.  Patient Queries


              1.Patient Worklist



               1.1 Schedule Sessions
               The appointments will appear on the Scheduled sessions page of the Patient worklist tab once
               the patient confirms the appointment by paying the doctor's consultation fees.
               Only the admin and doctor profiles will have access to this page. The admin can view the
               scheduled sessions of each doctor, as well as clinical information, reports, DICOM studies,
               and patient details. But the doctor is the only one who can examine his scheduled
               appointments. Other features include the ability to start, stop, and copy sessions, which
               allows the doctor to send a link to another doctor or patient's relative so they can join as
               guests.


                      : Doctor can view Clinical Information of a patient.


                     : Doctor can view Reports of a patient.


                    : Doctor can view the DICOM study. Ex: CT, MRI, XA, US, etc.

                       : Doctor can write Advisory Report from here.

                      : Doctor can view the Audio Video Recording from here.

                      : Doctor can view short summary written by an internal doctor from here.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[For Doctor Profile:

                       :  Doctor can start video call session using this start button.


                       : Doctor can end the session using this button.


                        : Doctor can send a link to another doctor or patient's relative so they can join as guests.


               The doctor can view the scheduled session for the particular period by using the date filter.
               The doctor can only begin a session whose session date is present date; sessions that are
               scheduled for the future or the past that have not yet started or will not start will not be able to
               start, and the start, end, and copy link buttons will not work for those sessions.




















               1.2 Completed Sessions
               The appointments will appear on the Completed sessions page after the doctor clicks on end
                         button after video call end. Admin/Doctor can see doctors remark on this page.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[2. Patient Queries



              2.1 Open Queries

               The patient may raise queries regarding his completed appointments or sessions, and those queries
               will show up on the Patient Queries tab's Open Queries page. The completed appointments must
               have been made within the last week; if the sessions were completed more than a week ago, the
               patient will not be able to raise or ask queries about those appointments. Only the admin and
               doctor profiles will have access to this page. Doctor gives response to the respective query
               of that appointment and that response sends to the patient via SMS.














               2.2 Closed Queries
















               The doctor responded message will appear in response column and that message will be sent to
               the respective patient via SMS and the query goes in closed queries page.]]></page></pages></Search>